Pinelands Folklife Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Field documentation arranged by fieldworker, Field photography descriptions are copied directly from B and C logs via Optical Character Recognition, so errors and abbreviations exist.
  - Sue Samuelson
    - Field photography on color slide film
      - Joseph Sahl's barn, Galloway, New Jersey; Grave decorations, Elwood, New Jersey, November 17, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CSS-039; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-CSS-039; 4 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-2, Joseph Sahl 's G-Galloway; 09GT barn which bear the words "The earth is the lord's and the fuliness thereof." G-Elwood; 12GT; 3-4, Cemetery "logs" (grave decorations) made by Sal Putiri Sr.
      - Cranberries, Tabernacle, New Jersey, November 4, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CSS-041; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-CSS-041; 7 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1, Dry picked, hand sorted cranberries. Picked by Mrs. Simons' son George G-Tabernacle; 25GT and given to her. Kept on screened-in front porch; 2-3, Cranberries in crates in nearby shed (part of the business operation); 4-5, Blueberry bushes, leaves turning, in back of Simons' yard; 6-7, Cranberries in buckets; 8, Chaff from cranberry sorting.
      - Interview with Eileen Homiller, house and yard, Lower Bank, New Jersey, November 10, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CSS-042; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-CSS-042; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1, Eileen Homilier in her kitchen. G-Lower Bank; 26GT; 2, Wire basket in Homiller's kitchen; 3, Wreath on interior door; 4, Silk (?) flower arrangement on window sill in living room; 5-6, Dried flower arrangements on tables in living room; 7, Bush in yard; 8, Detail of berries on bush; 9, Yard decorations (frogs); 10, Urns at end of front walk; 11, Elaine Thatcher and Eileen Homiller in front of Homiller house; 12, East end of house; 13, Elaine and Eileen in front of house; 14, East and north end of house; 15-16, Yard along north end of house; 17, Birdhouse at north end of house; 18, Yard and unidentified (see tape?) object at north end; 19, Windows or kitchen porch at south of house. Cats in windows; 20, Elaine and Eileen during walk around yard.
      - Yard walk at the Homillers, Lower Bank, New Jersey, November 10, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CSS-043; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-CSS-043; 18 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1, Herb garden at south end of Homiller house. G-Lower Bank; 26GT; 2, South end of Homiller house; 3, Fire pit in backyard; 4, Lawn furniture arranged around fire pit; 5, View from background looking south; 6, Backyard and rooster; 7, Backyard; 8, Backyard and and west end of house; 9, West end of house; 10, Detail of "love" painted on chimney; 11, Woods behind house; 12-13, Overgrown depression of some sort at edge of backyard; 14, Tree with autumn foliage in backyard; 15, Birdhouse; 16-17, North end of house. Eileen and Elaine in foreground; 18, East and north ends of house.
      - Yard, New Jersey, November 14, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CSS-044; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-CSS-044; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        G-Heidelberg Avenue; l2GT; 1, Backyard; 2, Birdhouse in backyard; 3, Shed in backyard used for grapevine wreath making and other activities. Elaine Thatcher and Helen Zimmer are on left; 4, Big glass jar containing birdseed and suspended from a tree near the dining area window; 5, Dog house and dog, Cricket; 6, Wind direction indicator (dark); 7, Another birdhouse; 8-10, East end of house and birdhouse (?) on terraced rise; 11, West end of house with Halloween/harvest decorations; 12, Carved pumpkins on outside ledge of living room window; 13, Outside door wreath; 14, Shell in front yard, covered with fallen leaves; 15, West (front) side of house from road (Heidellberg Ave.); 16, Sign at point where driveway meets road, "G. Zimmer"; 17, Yard decoration; 18, Tree with vine growing around it; 19, Tree that had been struck by lighting, cans around its base; 20, Birdhouse in garden.
      - Yard, New Jersey, November 14, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CSS-045; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-CSS-045; 5 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1, Birdhouse and garden. G-Heidelberg Avenue; 12GT; 2, Dark picture but can make out weathervane; 3, Boat and shed; 4-5, Arbor and north end of house and yard.
      - Cemetery, Egg Harbor City, New Jersey, November 19, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CSS-046; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-CSS-046; 19 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-7, General shots of the cemetery and particular plots showing the sandy soil and crushed green glass used to cover the plots. G-Egg Harbor City; 05GT; 9-10, Rows of graves in the sandy soil; 11, Plot outlined with bricks; 12, Detail of crushed glass; 13, Grave decorations: religious figurees, flowers; 14-15, Detail of glass; 15, has a flower encased in a glass jar; 16, Marker designating section of the cemetery; 17, General shot of cemetery row; 18-19, Plot with green glass and diamond inserts outlined in white.
      - Cemetery, Egg Harbor City, New Jersey, November 19, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CSS-047; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-CSS-047; 19 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-4, Schmidt plot. 2 and 3 show details of gate. 4 show grave in corner of plot set off by clay markers. G-Egg Harbor City Cemetery; 05GT; 5-7, Various graves and markers; 8, Partially painted clay markers in corner of one plot; 9, Clay markers which still have most of the silver paint on them; 10, Plot covered with colored glass which has intermixed with some white gravel from another plot; 12-14, Child's grave and headstone; 15, Cemetery and bell tower; 16-19, Graves with Christmas grave blankets.
      - Cemetery, Egg Harbor City, New Jersey, November 19, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CSS-048; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-CSS-048; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-3, Some rather decrepit looking plots covered with cement and glass. G-Egg Harbor City Cemetery; 05GT; 4-5, Long shots of some old graves marked only by the clay markers; 6-7, Close-ups of the graves in 4 and 5; 8-9, Grave marked by clay markers and covered with dead leaves. The clay markers still have much of their sliver paint still on; 10, Woven straw decoration on top of white urn/pedestal; 11, Plot where the graves are bound by sliver clay markers; 12, More graves with sliver markers; 13, General shot of older, sandy area of cemetery, looking towards the woods; 14-15, Plot covered with white gravel. Gravestone reads "Hiram Dotts/Sarah His Wife/And Family,"; 16-17, Glass covered plot which also includes a grave just covered with soil; 18, Plaque for bell tower; 19, Bell tower; 20, General view of newer part of cemetery (note abundance of graves).
      - Cemetery, Egg Harbor City, New Jersey, November 19, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CSS-049; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-CSS-049; 19 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1, General shot of the newer part of the cemetery (note abundance of grass as opposed to the sandy soil of the older part). G-Egg Harbor City Cemetery; OSGT; 2-3, Grave with photo of deceased in the marker; 4-5, Graves with flowers placed at the markers; 6, Grave decorated with little evergreen trees American flag, and bricks (?) outlining it near the headstone. Similar in use to clay markers in older part of cemetery (?); 7, Another grave similarly marked with pointed clay bricks as border; 8, Grave ornamentation: flowers (real and plastic), lamp, clay (?) seal loped markers as border; 9-10, Grave ornamentation: flowers, lamp, statue, evergreen, clay seal loped (?) markers as border; 11, White wooden cross as grave marker. Seen from rear in slide 10; 12, Entrance to Egg Harbor City Cemetery; 13, Memorial plaaque on entrance wall; 14, Cross (painted sliver) on entrance wall; 15-17, Christmas grave blankets on graves; 18, Labounsky graves with interesting (Russian?) crosses and photos of deceased in grave markers.
      - Cemetery, Egg Harbor City, New Jersey, November 19, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CSS-050; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-CSS-050; 19 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-2, Cavileer graves. Elaine Thatcher and I interviewed a member of this family during the project. G-Lower Bank; 26GT; 3-4, Yucca plants; 5, Walkway through cemetery; 6, Moses Leeds tombstone. Leeds family is a famous one in the region; 7-10, Gravesite decorated with yard ornaments (elves?); 11-12, Grapevine with grapes still on it; 13-14, Sever al plots. The one in the middle has a rock or bark covering. Another has a simple white cross (see front view in slide 15). In rear of photo are two graves covered with crushed green glass and white gravel, similar to those in the Egg Harbor City Cemetery; 15, White cross marker with plastic flowers; 16, Wood marker next to the white one in slide 15. It too has plastic flowers; 17, General shot of cemetery looking toward the road; 18, White urns(?) lined up against wall next to road; 19, Sandy plot.
      - Cemetery, Egg Harbor City, New Jersey, November 19, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CSS-051; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-CSS-051; 17 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-4, Grave ornamentation with various kinds of plastic flower arrangements. G-Lower Bank; 26GT; 5-10, Child's grave. Detail shots of various figures: cross/marker, bird (both sides), plastic dog, bunny; 11, General shot from outside cemetery gate; 12, Cemetery sign: "Our Garden of Memories"; 13, (Old) Lower Bank Methodist Church as seen from cemetery; 14, Church; 15, Church dates; 16-17, Sign pointing motorists to the Benjamin Franklin Bridge. These signs are found in Lower Bank, about 50 miles from where the bridge spans the Delaware River.
      - Yard walk at the Homillers, Lower Bank, New Jersey; Christmas grave decorations, New Jersey, November 10, 1983 to November 17, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CSS-052; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-CSS-052; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        Visit with Eileen Homiller of G-Lower Bank; 26GT. 01, Plant in Homillers' yard; 02, Area to north of yard, looking toward stable; 03, Chickens in stablee area; 04, Sarne as in 02, but looking more dierectly north. Emma's Farm Market, G-Elwood; 12GT; 05-07, Claude Angelo making bases of sphagnum moss for use in making grave blankets. He starts with a cedar slab and staples chicken wire to one side (05). Loads moss on the base (06) and staples chicken wire to other side (07); 08-10, Pile of completed sphagnum moss bases. On right in 10 are long slabs of cedar; 11, Moss bases awaiting decoration with greens; 12, Charlie (don't have last name, a cousin of Ralph's) and Ralph Putiri making grave blankets;. Elaine Thatcher in background; 13, Detail of construction of side and roof of greenhouse (interior); 14-19, Charlie making a grave blanket. Elaine Thatcher is on right in 14; 20, Charlie.
      - Christmas grave decorations, Elwood, New Jersey, November 17, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CSS-053; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-CSS-053; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
      - Christmas grave decorations, Elwood, New Jersey, November 17, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CSS-054; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-CSS-054; 18 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        Emma's Farm Market G-Elwood; 12GT; 01-05, Sal Sr. plastic poinsettias to cedar cross used for decoration of gravesite; 06, Finished cross; 07-08, Sal displaying finished cross to Elaine Thatcher; 01-11, Claude Angelo and basket of sphagnum moss. In 09, Carl Fleischhauer is on left, Ralph Putiri on right; 12, General shot of activity in the greenhouse. Left to right: Sal Putiri (in orange), Carl Fleischhauer, Elaine Thatcher, Charlie???, and Ralph Putiri; 13, Sal Sr. cutting green florist's foam for use in making a cemetery log; 14-18: Pushing foam into log. Elaine Thatcher holding microphone.
      - Christmas grave decorations, Elwood, New Jersey, December 10, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CSS-055; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-CSS-055; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        Emma's Farm Market G-Elwood; 12GT; 01, Sal Putiri Jr. posing by truck loaded with grave blankets; 02-03, Sal Putiri Sr. and Sal Putiri Jr. posing by truck; 04-05, Detail of some of the grave blankets in the truck; 06, George (don't have last name), a Putiri cousin, making grave blankets in the greenhouse at Emma's; 07-08, Pauline (don't have her last name), yet another Putiri cousin, making grave blankets; 09-16, Ralph Putiri making a cedar slab cross decorated with plastic poinsettias and bows. This cross was to be used as a decoration for Joseph in Putiri's (Ralph's mother) grave at the Oak Road Cemetery in Hammonton; 17, Sal Sr. in the greenhouse; 18-19, Cemetery "logs," decorated with greens, ruskus, poinsettias, bows and pine cones; 20, Decorated Christmas grave blanket lying on top of greens.
      - Christmas grave blankets and other cemetery decorations; Farm market, Elwood, New Jersey, December 10, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CSS-056; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-CSS-056; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        G-Elwood; 12GT; 0, Decorated Christmas grave blanket lying on top of some greenery; 02-03, Emma's Farm Market in late fall. Almost nothing left except grave blankets; 04-06, Tables with grave blankets, also used just as evergreen sprays for door decorations; 07-08, Flocked grave blanket, to be used on Josephine Putiri's (Ralph's late mother) grave at Oak Road Cemetery; 09, Piles of greenery to be used for grave blankets; 10-11, Completed grave blankets lying on ground near stand, to be sold to drive-in customers or to wholesalers or for prearranged orders; 12, Flowerpots and yard decorations (?) still on tables at farm market: Indian chief, goose, frogs; 13, Yard between Emma's Farm Market and the Putiri house, with Bozo the beagle in background; 14-15, Detail of dacorated grave blanket; 16, Ralph Putiri working on - grave blanket; 17-18, Ralph Putiri posing with completed decoration; 19-20, Sal Putiri Sr. making the cedar slab bases for the cemetery decorations they call a log
      - Christmas grave blankets and decorations; Christmas decorations on graves at Oak Road Cemetery, Elwood, New Jersey, December 10, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CSS-057; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-CSS-057; 18 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        Emma's Farm Market G-Elwood; 12GT; 01, Sal Putiri Sr. making the cedar slab base for the Christmas grave decoration they call a log; 02, Log in process of being decorated; 03-05, Completed logs; 06-08, Pauline (don't have last name), a Putiri cousin, making grave blankets; 09, Red bow used as decoration; 10, Decorated grave blanket; 11, The greenhouse next to Emma's which serves as the work area for making grave blankets; 12-18, Various shots of Christmas decorations on graves at G-Oak Road Cemetery; 11GT.
      - Hog butchering near Sweetwater, New Jersey, December 10, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CSS-058; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-CSS-058; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        Hog butchering near G-Sweetwater; 12GT; 01-02, Ralph Putiri and Joe Colache examining trussed up pigs. Man on right in 01 is unidentified; 03-04, .Joe Colache cleaning up; 05, Pig's head and beer cans; 06-08, Pigs' heads and beer cans; 06-11, Matthew Colache and pigs' heads; 12-13, Matthew Colache. 13 has wheelbarrow with pigs legs in it; 14, Joe Colache and Ralph Putiri; 15-17, .Joe and his friends who helped to slaughter the pigs, with pigs head. The man in front with Joe was teased as being an "outsider" from north Jersey; 18-19, Trussed pigs; 20, Pigs' legs in wheelbarrow.
      - Hog butchering near Sweetwater, New Jersey, December 10, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CSS-059; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-CSS-059; 5 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        High butchering near G-Sweetwater; 12GT; 01, Joe Colache examining pig's leg; 02-05, Loading slaughtered pigs into a van. They will be left in it overnight to cool and thus be easier to butcher.
      - Cemetery festival, Hammonton, New Jersey, July 16, 1984, AFC 1991/023: CSS84-001; Sue Samuelson; PFP-84-CSS-001; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
      - Our Lady of Mount Carmel celebration, Hammonton, New Jersey, July 16, 1984, AFC 1991/023: CSS84-002; Sue Samuelson; PFP-84-CSS-002; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        Our Lady of Mt. Carmel Celebration, G-Hammonton: 11GT; 1-2, Devotional area. People contributed money to have candles lit. In the alley next to St. Joseph' s church; 3, looking down alley to picnic and vendor area; 4, Statue of Mary near devotional area; 5, Raffle stand for Deborah Hospital. (Car is being raffled); 6-7, St. Joseph's Church, focal point for the celebration. 7 has sign listing masses for the day; 8-10, Crowd shots, including souvenir vendors. Man in center of 9 was selling a bizarre item; he blew into a straw which would make the paper ears on his head stand up; 11-12, St. Joseph's Church Hall, front and side views. 12 also has lemonade truck; 13, People lining Third St. waiting for procession; 14, Table with souvenirs. (See also PFP-84-CSS-001-13); 15, Poster announcing celebration; 16, Main Street; 17, Parade arrives on Main Street; 18, Rescue squad truck begins parade; 19, The souvenir table again; 20, Parade grand marshall (mayor?) in red convertible.
      - Our Lady of Mt. Carmel Celebration, Hammonton, New Jersey, July 16, 1984, AFC 1991/023: CSS84-003; Sue Samuelson; PFP-84-CSS-003; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        Our Lady of Mt. Carmel Celebration in G-Hammonton; 11GT; 1-10, The parade begins with marching members of the Society of Mt. Carmel bearing banners of St. Joseph and American and Italian flags. In the middle of 5 the cluster of people includes New Jersey's Governor Kean. Altar boys are in 10; 11-12, The procession of saints begins as souvenir vendors crowd into the picture; 13-14, Parade watchers on Main Street; 15, Parade watches in yard on Third Street; 16-17, two well-dressed ladies on their way to church; 18-19, Gov. Kean and his coterie meeting and greeting parade watchers; 20, The procession of saints begins to march up Third Street.
      - Our Lady of Mt. Carmel Celebration, Hammonton, New Jersey, July 16, 1984, AFC 1991/023: CSS84-004; Sue Samuelson; PFP-84-CSS-004; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        Our Lady of Mt. Carmel Celebration in G-Hammonton; 11GT; 1, Banners at beginning of procession and flags; 2-3, St. Joseph's statue on cart. Note on this and other statues the money pinned to it; 4, Statue of St. Lucy; 5-6 St. Rita; 7, Statue of Jesus (Sacred Heart?) on float (larger cart); 8-9, St. Rocco (?); 10, St .Jude; 11, Statue of the Mother of Peace (Mary); 12, Unidentified statue; 13-6, Middle-distance shots of procession of saints; 17-18, Statue of Mary on floral-decorated float; 19, Float attendants pinning on money; 20, St. ?? Palllotti with attendants leaning on cart.
      - Our Lady of Mt. Carmel Celebration, Hammonton, New Jersey, July 16, 1984, AFC 1991/023: CSS84-005; Sue Samuelson; PFP-84-CSS-005; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        Our Lady of Mt. Carmel Festival in G-Hammonton: 11GT; 1-3, Procession surrounding statue of Our Lady of Mt. Carmel; 4-5, Band preceding the statue; 6, Statue and banner; 7, Crowd behind the statue, rear of procession; 8, Statue and crowds; 9, Balloon vendor; 10, Man and woman in red, white and green (Italian colors) caps; 11, Another shot of a Mary stature (Not Our Lady of Mt. Carmel), the one in PFP-84-CSS-004-17/18. Man on tractor pulling the float is at left; 12-13, Crowd in front of St. Joseph's Church as procession begins to enter church; 14, Souvenir dolls on sticks; booth for St. Joseph's School alumni; 15, Parade watchers on Lawn chairs next to the res cue squad truck; 16, Rescue squad food booth with menu; 17-18, Carnival area; 19, Another menu for food booth; 20, Food and beer booth for the Society of Our Lady of the Assumption.
      - Our Lady of Mt. Carmel Celebration, Hammonton, New Jersey, July 16, 1984, AFC 1991/023: CSS84-006; Sue Samuelson; PFP-84-CSS-006; 2 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        Our Lady of Mt. Carmel Celebration, G-Hammonton; 11GT; 1, Religious banner at site of booth for the society of Our Lady of the Assumption; 2, Raffle sign for Hammonton High School Booster Club.
    - Field recordings on reel-to-reel audio tape
      - R log (reel-to-reel log), Sue Samuelson; 47 manuscript pages (8.5 x 14 inch or smaller) (Box-folder 17/159)
      - Interview with Helen Fasick, Community Relations Officer, Fort Dix, New Jersey, part 1, September 23, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23984; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-RSS-001; RXA 6049; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch)
        G-Ft. Dix; 19GT
      - Interview with Helen Fasick, Community Relations Officer, Fort Dix, New Jersey, part 2, September 23, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23985; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-RSS-002; RXA 6050; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch)
      - Interview with Helen Fasick, Community Relations Officer, Fort Dix, New Jersey, part 3, September 23, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23986; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-RSS-003; RXA 6051; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch)
      - Interview with Teresa Litely and grape stomping contest, Renault Winery, Bremen Avenue, Egg Harbor City, New Jersey, September 24, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23987; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-RSS-004; RXA 6052; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch); Elaine Thatcher
        G-Renault Winery; 05GT
      - Interview with Ralph Putiri and Salvatore (Sal) Putiri, Sr., Hammonton, New Jersey, part 1, September 28, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23988; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-RSS-005; RXA 6053; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch); Elaine Thatcher
        G-Elwood; 12GT
      - Interview with Ralph Putiri and Salvatore (Sal) Putiri, Sr., Hammonton, New Jersey, part 2, September 28, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23989; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-RSS-006; RXA 6054; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch); Elaine Thatcher
      - Interview with Lieutenant Colonel Craig C. McNab, Public Affairs Officer, Fort Dix, New Jersey, part 1, September 29, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23990; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-RSS-007; RXA 6055; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch)
      - Interview with Lieutenant Colonel Craig C. McNab, Public Affairs Officer, Fort Dix, New Jersey, part 2, September 29, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23991; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-RSS-008; RXA 6056; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch)
      - Interview with Earl Piper and driving around area, New Jersey, part 1, September 29, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23992; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-RSS-009; RXA 6057; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch)
      - Interview with Earl Piper and driving around area, New Jersey, part 2, September 29, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23993; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-RSS-010; RXA 6058; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch)
      - VFW pig roast; Interview at the pig roast; Band music, New Jersey, October 1, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23994; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-RSS-011; RXA 6059; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch)
        G-Browns Mills; 21GT. Interviewee: Hazelton (Hazy) Dilkes
      - Church service (Harvest Home), St. John's United Church of Christ, London Street and Beethoven, Egg Harbor City, New Jersey, part 1, October 2, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23995; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-RSS-012; RXA 6060; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch); Jens Lund
        G-Egg Harbor City; 05GT
      - Church service (Harvest Home), St. John's United Church of Christ, London Street and Beethoven, Egg Harbor City, New Jersey, part 2, October 2, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23996; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-RSS-013; RXA 6061; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch); Jens Lund
      - Church service (Harvest Home), St. John's United Church of Christ, London Street and Beethoven, Egg Harbor City, New Jersey, part 3, October 2, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23997; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-RSS-014; RXA 6062; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch); Jens Lund
      - Interview with Helen Zimmer and George Zimmer: food preparation and mealtime, Egg Harbor, New Jersey, part 1, October 12, 1983, AFC 1991/023: AFS 23998; Sue Samuelson; PFP-83-RSS-015; RXA 6063; 1 audiotape reel (7 inch); Elaine Thatcher